Guide to the Brown Brothers Harriman Records 1696-1973, 1995 (bulk, 1820-1968) MS 78
New-York Historical Society
- Series I. Historical Files (1699-1974), 1820-1968; 39 Linear feet (81 document boxes, 6 oversize boxes, 12 volumes)
  - Subseries A. Chronological Files (1796-1970), 1818-1968; 31 document boxes, XX OS boxes, 6 volumes
    - Newspaper coverage of merger: photocopies and photostats, 1930 December 12 (Offsite-box OS 1, Folder 21)
    - Life clipping: "Bull market gives life to citadel of U.S. capitalism", 1946 January 7 (Offsite-box OS 1, Folder 22)
    - First daybook: glossies, 1825 October 4-1828 March 4 (Offsite-box OS 2, Folder 1)
    - Goodrich plan of New York at the time of Brown Brothers' establishment: glossy, 1827 (Offsite-box OS 2, Folder 2)
    - Watercolor of Mobile, Alabama: photo, 1841 (Offsite-box OS 2, Folder 3)
    - Brown Brothers instruction book: photocopies of originals at New York Public Library, 1842-1852 (Offsite-box OS 2, Folder 4)
    - West side of Broadway, Exchange Alley to Morris Street; Savannah, Georgia: images, 1855 (Offsite-box OS 2, Folder 5)
    - John Crosby Brown appointment as Commissioner of Common School, New York City: original, glossy, 1873 (Offsite-box OS 2, Folder 6)
    - Investors' Supplement with Brown Bros. & Co. advertisement: mounted original, photocopy, 1875 June 26 (Offsite-box OS 2, Folder 7)
    - Philadelphia office interior: photo, 1899-1900 (Offsite-box OS 2, Folder 8)
    - Fabrics and Fibers Journal clipping on Irish linen merchants (1941), 1800s (Offsite-box OS 2, Folder 9)
    - London office, 123 Pall Mall: photo, c. 1900 (Offsite-box OS 2, Folder 10)
    - Portrait of Alexander Brown and Sons: photo, negative, correspondence (Offsite-box OS 2, Folder 11)
    - Cartoon of New York and Philadelphia Brown Brothers offices' baseball game, correspondence, 1921 (Offsite-box OS 2, Folder 12)
    - Second Prussian loan: dinner - photo, menu, humorous prospectus, 1927 October 22 (Offsite-box OS 2, Folder 13)
    - Corner of conference room in partners' area, 1865 building: photo, c. 1928 (Offsite-box OS 2, Folder 14)
    - Fortune clippings: "Wall Street's Influential Analysts"; "Wall Streeters Who Were Right", 1957 January, 1958 May (Offsite-box OS 2, Folder 15)
    - Main banking floor platform: photo, 1959 (Offsite-box OS 2, Folder 16)
    - Business Week cover article: "Hardy Survivors of a Dying Breed"; issue, photos, 1958 September (Offsite-box OS 3, Folder 1)
    - "Personality of a Bank": background clippings, 1959 (Offsite-box OS 4, Folder 1)
    - Partners' group photo: prints, clipping, 1965 November 8 (Offsite-box OS 4, Folder 2)
    - Clippings, 1965 (Offsite-box OS 4, Folder 3)
    - Clippings, 1966 (Offsite-box OS 4, Folder 4)
    - J. E. Banks' Institutional Investment Guides; comments, 1966 (Offsite-box OS 4, Folder 5)
    - Palo Alto Times issue, 1968 January 30 (Offsite-box OS 4, Folder 6)
    - 150th anniversary: advertising and publicity - clippings, 1968 May (Offsite-box OS 4, Folder 7)
    - 150th anniversary: Sun Valley - press clippings, 1968 September (Offsite-box OS 4, Folder 8)
    - 150th anniversary: staff party - program, 1968 October (Offsite-box OS 4, Folder 9)
    - 150th anniversary: staff party - press coverage, New York Times clippings, 1968 October (Offsite-box OS 4, Folder 10)
    - 150th anniversary: staff party - press coverage, New York Times full issue, October 10, 1968 October (Offsite-box OS 4, Folder 11)
    - 150th anniversary: logo design, separation, 1968 (Offsite-box OS 4, Folder 12)
    - Photograph of Walter Good at annual meeting, for "Personality of a Bank", 1968 (Offsite-box OS 4, Folder 13)
    - Certificate of merit from Printing Industries of Metropolitan New York for design of "Personality of a Bank", 1968 (Offsite-box OS 4, Folder 14)
    - Original pseudo-historical sketches for Partners in Banking by John Carnes (also used in 1967 "Personality of a Bank"), 1959 (Offsite-box OS 5, Folder 1)
    - Group photos of the partners taken for "Personality of a Bank", 1959 (Offsite-box OS 5, Folder 2)
    - Group photo of partners, 1962 April 23 (Offsite-box OS 5, Folder 3)
    - Esquire clipping: "The Wall Street Establishment", 1966 June (Offsite-box OS 5, Folder 4)
    - Galley proofs for "Personality of a Bank", 2nd edition, with John A. Kouwenhoven corrections, 1966 November (Offsite-box OS 5, Folder 5)
    - Historical Files: photo used in Partners in Banking, 1967 February (Offsite-box OS 5, Folder 6)
    - 150th anniversary: documentation of press coverage, 1968 (Offsite-box OS 5, Folder 7)
    - 150th anniversary: Partners in Banking - publication, reviews, 1968 (Offsite-box OS 5, Folder 8)
    - Clippings, 1969 (Offsite-box OS 5, Folder 9)
    - Rock Island case: Brown Brothers Harriman, Union Pacific - clippings, 1969-1970 (Offsite-box OS 5, Folder 10)
    - Clippings, 1970 (Offsite-box OS 5, Folder 11)
    - 100th anniversary dinner seating plan, 1925 December 18 (Drawer OS D1900)
    - First letter book, Brown Brothers, 1825-1827 (Offsite-box BBH-3, Volume 1)
    - John Crosby Brown letter book, 1861 February - 1869 March (Offsite-box BBH-1, Volume 2)
    - Annual accounts, Brown Brothers, 1868 (Offsite-box BBH-1, Volume 3)
    - Partners' private and confidential letters, 1888-1898 (Offsite-box BBH-1, Volume 4)
    - John Crosby Brown letter book, 1895-1900 (Offsite-box BBH-1, Volume 5)
    - John Crosby Brown private and confidential correspondence, 1906-1907 (Offsite-box BBH-1, Volume 6)
  - Subseries B. Subject Files (1708-1970), 31 document boxes XX OS boxes, 6 volumes
    The subseries documents Brown Brothers Harriman and its predecessor companies' internal and external connections with correspondent banks and branch offices, as well as with organizations, investors, and individuals worldwide. They provide information on its offices, activities, and agents, including investment in the Collins steamship line and the deaths of Brown family members aboard Arctic in 1854; details of the 1931 merger with the Harriman interests; deeds, plans, and purchases of property at and around the firm's New York offices at 59 Wall Street; and financing during World Wars I and II. The co-partnership files give details of the additions to the firm's partners, and their loss through retirement or death, from 1915 to 1953.
    Highlights include detailed examples of Brown Brothers & Co.'s letters of credit, which provided access to funds for individuals and organizations internationally, including a list of London locations that would cash travelers checks with an accompanying note from John D. Rockefeller Jr.; W. Averell Harriman's unused $10,000 letter of credit while he was roving ambassador for President Franklin Roosevelt in 1942; and, from the Philadelphia office, a credit draft endorsed with withdrawals from Hawaii through South and East Asia to France and Italy on a 1928 world tour by a Brown Brothers customer. An indexed collection of letter abstracts and other communications received and sent by the Philadelphia office of Brown Brothers & Co. provides a snapshot of bank operations nationally and internationally, including foreign exchange issues, in the period 1885-1904.
    The subseries is arranged alphabetically by name of person, place, event, or other appropriate subject heading.
    Placed before the alphabetical listing (which begins with "Alex. Brown & Sons") is a group of Case History files, which were prepared for inclusion in Partners in Banking, but not eventually used in that format. Information from these proposed Case Histories on the merger of Bangor Aroostook Railroad with the Punta Alegre sugar manufacturing company, and Brown Brothers Harriman's role in the development of Columbia, MD, became instead extended captions describing photographs at the end of the book (pp. 206-208). Original order of these materials has been retained.
    The organization of materials in the subseries is not always consistent, and is often duplicative. For example, information on overseas banks is grouped into Foreign Banks, but there are separate files for Banque de France and Norge Bank; information on Punta Alegre exists in both the Case Files and in alphabetical order; and materials pertaining to the firm's 150th anniversary celebrations are included under both "Sesquicentennial" and "Sun Valley", as well as in the "1968" materials in Subseries I.A. Chronological Files. Material originally filed under "Metropolitan Museum of Art" has been included in the folder "Crosby Brown Collection of Musical Instruments," because it is specifically on that subject. Consulting the card catalog to the collection available in the Reading Room, which provides item-level indexing, may be helpful in resolving these inconsistencies.
    Materials within subject headings were originally in chronological order, and that has been retained in smaller files. In larger files, materials have been organized into types (e.g., clippings, correspondence, cross-reference sheets, images) for clearer identification, and then ordered chronologically.
    Volumes 7-12, which were originally included in the Subject files, have been removed and are listed in chronological order at the end of the container list.
    All information pertaining to Brown Brothers' Wall Street offices, which was originally out of order (including a chronology found together with some visual materials), is now included in the "Property" files. Correspondence between partner Thatcher Brown and Museum of the City of New York director Harding Scholle from the 1940s indicates that the original deeds to the Wall Street property from 1699 and 1708 are on permanent loan to the Museum, available at that time to be borrowed on request.
    Various materials found elsewhere in the collection have been added to the Subject files as appropriate. Binders containing draft and final data printouts with information on attendees at the 1968 Sun Valley sesquicentennial gathering are now included in the "Sun Valley" materials as boxes 55-57. Their date order is not consistent because these materials are housed in different-sized boxes.
    Records almost exclusively to do with co-partnership agreements had been culled from the firm's original records for inclusion in Thatcher Brown's 1950 book Brown Brothers & Co. [and] Brown Brothers Harriman & Co., 1900-1950. They were then further culled in early June 1964 and were labeled as awaiting John Kouwenhoven's return to be reviewed.
    Some files labeled as originating from the Tax Department are now included under that designation. General files from the Department are in chronological order, followed by client-specific folders in alphabetical order by last name. Information in them includes some of the individuals also represented in Subseries I.C. People.
    Two books of stockholder records for Wall and Hanover Street Realty Co. are included as Volumes 9 and 10. Folders of Brown Bros. & Co. correspondence marked with Kouwenhoven's Subject designation, but not included in the original filing cabinets and not annotated, have been added there.
    Extracts of letters and other communications compiled into a volume (with index), which became disbound and is labeled in Kouwenhoven's handwriting as having originated from the Philadelphia office, is now included with those materials. There is some variation in the box order of these items because they are housed in different sized boxes
    Various oversize photographic materials found organized separately in the Records but originally marked as belonging to the Subject files are now included here. Two photographs of lower Manhattan showing the Brown Brothers building at 59 Wall Street were not labeled with a subject heading; these have been added to the "Property" files.
    Liverpool (England) -- Commerce.; Letters of credit.; Insurance; Cotton trade; World War, 1939-1945 -- Finance; World War, 1914-1918 -- Finance; Merchants -- England -- Liverpool -- History -- 19th century.; Harriman, W. Averell (William Averell), 1891-1986; Harriman, Edward Henry, 1848-1909; Bush, Prescott Sheldon, 1895-1972; Brown, William, Sir, 1784-1864; Brown, William Adams, 1865-1943; Brown, Thatcher Magoun, 1876-1954; Brown, John Crosby, 1838-1909; Brown, James, 1863-1943; Brown, Mary Elizabeth, 1842-1918; Roosa, Robert V.; Lovett, Robert A. (Robert Abercrombie), 1895-1986; Bangor and Aroostook Railroad Company; Collins Line; Crosby Brown Collection of Musical Instruments (Metropolitan Museum of Art); Union Theological Seminary (New York, N.Y.)
    - Aroostook Construction Co.: Voting Trust agreement, 1902-1912, 1919 (Offsite-box 31, Folder 13)
    - Bangor & Aroostook Railroad: photos, 1902-1906 (Offsite-box 31, Folder 14)
    - Bangor & Aroostook Railroad: photos, 1902-1906 (Offsite-box 31, Folder 15)
    - Bangor & Aroostook Railroad Co.: letters and contracts of sale, agreements, 1911-1923 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 1)
    - Aroostook Construction Co.: contracts, 1912-1913 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 2)
    - Bangor & Aroostook Railroad Co.: J. Kouwenhoven interview with Mr. Douglas, 1965 September 13 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 3)
    - Bangor & Aroostook Railroad Co./ Punta Alegre Sugar Co., 1891-1927 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 4)
    - Bangor & Aroostook Railroad Co.: Punta Alegre Sugar Co. - images, 1913, 1952-1958 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 5)
    - Bangor & Aroostook Railroad Co.: Punta Alegre Sugar Co., 1930-1940 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 6)
    - Bangor & Aroostook Railroad Co.: Punta Alegre Sugar Co., 1960-1970 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 7)
    - British Assets Trust Ltd.: credit, 1963 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 1)
    - Prudential Assurance Co. Ltd.: loan, 1955 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 2)
    - Fritz Blankenstein "sealed envelope" account, 1939-1966 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 3)
    - Houston Oil Co. of Texas, 1902-1956 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 4)
    - Vertol Division of the Boeing Corporation, 1943-1964 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 5)
    - Export credit documents: Brown Shipley & Co. - photocopies, 1962 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 6)
    - Irrevocable letters of credit: Forte, Dupee, Sawyer & Co., 1964 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 7)
    - Irwin-Harrisons-Whitney tea importers, 1960s (Offsite-box 33, Folder 8)
    - Ira Haupt Co./ Allied Crude Vegetable Oil Refining Corp., 1963-1965 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 9)
    - Alex. Brown & Sons: letterbooks - photocopies of originals in Library of Congress, 1861-1863 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 10)
    - Alex. Brown & Sons: letterbook - photocopies of originals in Library of Congress, 1863 January - July (Offsite-box 33, Folder 11)
    - Alex. Brown & Sons: cross-reference sheets, 1860s - 1966 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 12)
    - Alex. Brown & Sons: list of old books in record vault, 1964 May (Offsite-box 33, Folder 13)
    - American Museum of Natural History re putative storing of specimens at 59 Wall Street, 1869-1870, 1968 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 14)
    - American Red Cross: chronology of E. Roland Harriman's positions, 1951-1967 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 1)
    - Ship Armata: image, correspondence, 1962-1967 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 2)
    - Atlantic Mutual Insurance Co.: cross-references, ship insurance information including Mary Celeste, 1836-1951 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 3)
    - Baltimore: background research, 1800-1966 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 4)
    - Baltimore: view, directory, street scene, ship Alexander, Brown Partners, Brown's Wharf - photos, 1801-1869 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 5)
    - Baltimore: cross-reference sheets, 1808-1964 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 6)
    - Baltimore: Alex. Brown profit and loss statements; securities list, 1815-1831, 1896 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 7)
    - Baltimore: biographical information on Brown-family partners in Alex. Brown & Co., 1834-1931 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 8)
    - Baltimore: powers of attorney, Brown Bros. & Co., NY, to Alex. Brown & Co., 1882 February 25-1905 January (Offsite-box 34, Folder 9)
    - Bank of California: cross-reference sheets, 1863-1864 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 10)
    - Bank of California: background research, image, 1906, 1910, 1964 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 11)
    - Banking: photocopies of articles, 1941-1968 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 12)
    - Banking Officer Development Program at Brown Brothers Harriman, [1960s] (Offsite-box 34, Folder 13)
    - Banks (domestic): cross-reference sheets, 1825-1966 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 14)
    - Banks (domestic): information on individual banks, 1906-1967 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 15)
    - House of Baring: indexed photocopy of article, 1949 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 16)
    - Boston office: cross-reference sheets, 1833-1963 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 17)
    - Boston office: background research, 1844-1965 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 18)
    - Boston office: Brattle Street-image, 1845 (Offsite-box 35, Folder 1)
    - Boston office: powers of attorney, 1875 September 28-1901 July 23 (Offsite-box 35, Folder 2)
    - Boston office: powers of attorney from Brown Bros. & Co., NY, 1905 June 15-1926 June 30 (Offsite-box 35, Folder 3)
    - Boston office: documents and correspondence, circa 1906-1928 Dec 21 (Offsite-box 35, Folder 4)
    - Boston office: employees, banking floor, Quarter-Century Club-photos, 1913, 1959, 1967 (Offsite-box 35, Folder 5)
    - Boston office: business forms, 1920s (Offsite-box 35, Folder 6)
    - Boston office: business forms, 1930s (Offsite-box 35, Folder 7)
    - Boston office: business forms, 1940s (Offsite-box 35, Folder 8)
    - Boston office: business forms, 1950s (Offsite-box 35, Folder 9)
    - Boston office: business forms, 1960s, undated (Offsite-box 35, Folder 10)
    - Boys' Club of New York, 1962-1968 (Offsite-box 35, Folder 11)
    - Thatcher M. Brown III: memos on travel and foreign investment, 1964-1967 (Offsite-box 35, Folder 12)
    - Brown Brothers & Co.: correspondence, balance sheets, 1900-1902 (Offsite-box 35, Folder 13)
    - Brown Brothers & Co.: correspondence - sale of securities, travel, Brown Shipley, 1905-1906 (Offsite-box 35, Folder 14)
    - Brown Brothers & Co.: correspondence - cotton loan, Merchant Marine insurance, Roumanian loan, 1914 (Offsite-box 35, Folder 15)
    - Brown Brothers & Co.: correspondence - firm business, 1914-1921 (Offsite-box 36, Folder 1)
    - Brown Brothers & Co.: correspondence - French loan, English municipals, French medal, Belgium, 1916-1917 (Offsite-box 36, Folder 2)
    - Brown Brothers & Co.: correspondence - Cecil Spring-Rice, partnership papers with Brown Shipley & Co., 1917-1918 (Offsite-box 36, Folder 3)
    - Brown Brothers & Co.: correspondence - separation from Brown Shipley & Co., 1917-1918 (Offsite-box 36, Folder 4)
    - Brown Brothers & Co.: correspondence between James Brown and D. Wheeler Brown, 1917-1920 (Offsite-box 36, Folder 5)
    - Brown Brothers & Co.: correspondence - George H. Frazier, business matters (Offsite-box 36, Folder 6)
    - Brown Brothers & Co.: correspondence - James Brown Legion of Honor, Canadian financing, first settlement of Rachel B. Brown estate, 1918-1920 (Offsite-box 36, Folder 7)
    - Brown Brothers & Co.: correspondence - Manaos Improvement, Ltd., Chamber of Commerce of the United States, 1918-1920 (Offsite-box 36, Folder 8)
    - Brown Brothers & Co.: correspondence - uniform deed of trust, International Trade Conference, Federal Reserve Board, 1919 (Offsite-box 36, Folder 9)
    - Brown Brothers & Co.: correspondence - Edlmann partnership, business contacts, Charles D. Dickey, 1920-1921 (Offsite-box 36, Folder 10)
    - Brown Brothers & Co.: correspondence - estate issues, partnership, George H. Frazier, 1920-1922 (Offsite-box 36, Folder 11)
    - Brown Brothers & Co.: correspondence - Bryce, British Empire Chamber of Commerce, Herbert Hoover, 1922, 1924-1925 (Offsite-box 37, Folder 1)
    - Brown Shipley & Co.: background research, 1809-1965 (Offsite-box 37, Folder 2)
    - Brown Shipley & Co.: cross-reference sheets, 1812-1847 (Offsite-box 37, Folder 3)
    - Brown Shipley & Co.: images, 1818-1848 (Offsite-box 37, Folder 4)
    - Brown Shipley & Co.: Joseph Shipley correspondence-originals and photocopies, 1819 September 6-1842 September 19 (Offsite-box 37, Folder 5)
    - Brown Shipley & Co.: ledgers S-Z, 1836-1840 (Offsite-box 37, Folder 6)
    - Brown Shipley & Co.: ledgers S-Z, 1836-1840 (Offsite-box 37, Folder 7)
    - Brown Shipley & Co.: ledgers S-Z, 1836-1840 (Offsite-box 37, Folder 8)
    - Brown Shipley & Co.: W. & J. Brown, Brown Bros. Co. correspondence - originals and letterpress copies, 1837, 1844 (Offsite-box 37, Folder 9)
    - Brown Shipley & Co.: ledgers E-K, 1841-1845 (Offsite-box 37, Folder 10)
    - Brown Shipley & Co.: ledgers E-K, 1841-1845 (Offsite-box 38, Folder 1)
    - Brown Shipley & Co.: ledgers E-K, 1841-1845 (Offsite-box 38, Folder 2)
    - Brown Shipley & Co.: original letters to Brown Bros. & Co., 1844 August (Offsite-box 38, Folder 3)
    - Brown Shipley & Co.: original letters to Brown Bros. & Co., 1844 September (Offsite-box 38, Folder 4)
    - Brown Shipley & Co.: cross-reference sheets, 1850-1868 (Offsite-box 38, Folder 5)
    - Brown Shipley & Co.: images of Liverpool, 1966 correspondence, 1856-1888 (Offsite-box 38, Folder 6)
    - Brown Shipley & Co.: Joseph Shipley, Brown Shipley, and other Brown correspondence-originals and photocopies, 1857 October 10-1885 October 6 (Offsite-box 38, Folder 7)
    - Brown Shipley & Co.: cross-reference sheets, 1888-1916 (Offsite-box 38, Folder 8)
    - Brown Shipley & Co.: Supplement to the London American-image, 1896 (Offsite-box 38, Folder 9)
    - Brown Shipley & Co.: correspondence of and about Montagu Norman - originals, 1899 December 29-1916 January (Offsite-box 38, Folder 10)
    - Brown Shipley & Co.: background research, 1902-1929 (Offsite-box 38, Folder 11)
    - Brown Shipley & Co.: correspondence on partnership issues - originals, 1913 July 11-1915 December 1 (Offsite-box 38, Folder 12)
    - Brown Shipley & Co.: Sir Alexander H. Brown correspondence - originals and letterpress copies, 1913 December 4-1914 June 11 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 1)
    - Brown Shipley & Co.: letters to Brown family members about the War - originals, 1914 August 6-1916 July 31 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 2)
    - Brown Shipley & Co.: correspondence - originals and letterpress copies, 1914 August-1916 March (Offsite-box 39, Folder 3)
    - Brown Shipley & Co.: powers of attorney, 1915 January 15, 1916 January 22 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 4)
    - Brown Shipley & Co.: cross-reference sheets, 1917-1965 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 5)
    - Brown Shipley & Co.: power of attorney, 1918 January 25 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 6)
    - Brown Shipley & Co.: signature lists, 1918-1932 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 7)
    - Brown Shipley & Co.: partners room, partners, Founders Court-images, 1922-1951 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 8)
    - Brown Shipley & Co.: background research, 1927-1967 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 9)
    - Brown Shipley & Co.: letter about travelers' letters of credit, 1936 March 18 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 10)
    - Brown Shipley & Co.: Brown portraits in Frick Art Reference Library, 1964 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 11)
    - Brown Shipley & Co.: brochure "Plan Your Finance with Brown Shipley & Co. Ltd.", 1967 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 12)
    - Brown Shipley & Co.: correspondence to Sarah B. Brown re research, family, 1960s (Offsite-box 39, Folder 13)
    - Bruderman-Robert Brunner (clients), 1919-1965 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 14)
    - Chicago office: cross-reference sheets, 1862-1964 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 15)
    - Chicago office: offices, S. LaSalle St., Gillette photos for "Personality of a Bank"- images, 1873, 1927, 1965 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 16)
    - Chicago office: background research, clippings, 1929-1970 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 17)
    - Chicago office: power of attorney, 1931 January (Offsite-box 39, Folder 18)
    - Chicago office: background on Grand Rapids agency, 1968 September (Offsite-box 39, Folder 19)